<resources>
    <string name="app_name">COVID-19</string>
    <array name="autosize_text_sizes">
        <item>10sp</item>
        <item>12sp</item>
        <item>20sp</item>
        <item>40sp</item>
        <item>100sp</item>
    </array>
    <string name="List"> How Can I Treat Coronavirus Symptoms? \n
The main symptoms of the novel coronavirus are fever, cough and shortness of breath: \n \n 1. For a Fever \n *Take a fever reducer. If you choose to or if your fever is very high, you can take a fever reducer. Acetaminophen is what is usually recommended. While ibuprofen is also a fever reducer, there is some concern that it may not be safe to take with the novel coronavirus. More research needs to be done to know for sure.\n *Stay hydrated. Fevers usually cause sweating, which means loss of water from your body. Drink lots of fluids (preferably water or juice and not soda or high sugar beverages that might make you thirstier). Caffeinated beverages are not recommended.\n *Rest. Your body needs energy to fight the virus. Just rest up and let your body do its job.\n \n 2. For a Cough \n *Sip on drinks throughout the day. Not only will this keep your throat moist and comfortable, it will help keep you hydrated. \n *Drink warm beverages, like tea or broth. These heat up the airways, keep you hydrated and break up any mucus you might have in your throat and upper airway. \n *Try a teaspoon of honey in hot tea or hot water. A little bit of honey tends to soothe a sore throat. However, children under 1 year old should not try honey \n *Breathe in steam. Use a hot shower, humidifier, vaporizer or other means of making steam. It will soothe a sore throat and open your airways, making it easier to breathe. \n *Gargle salt water. While it is not scientifically proven to help, many people swear that salt water helps their sore throat. There is no harm in trying, and it might help you. Use 1 teaspoon of salt in 8 ounces of warm water. Make sure you spit it out and disinfect the sink afterward. \n *Eat a frozen treat. The coldness may help numb the pain and soothe your throat if it is sore from coughing.\n *Suck on cough drops, lozenges or hard candy. These will keep your mouth and throat moist.\n *Try cough medicine. If you have a wet cough with lots of mucus, you want to take an expectorant to help get the mucus out. If you have a dry cough, a cough suppressant is what you want. Make sure you choose the right one.\n *For pain, try acetaminophen. Sometimes a lot of coughing can be painful. A pain reliever can take the edge off.\n \n 3. For Shortness of Breath\n *Take slow breaths. Slowing things down can help you start breathing again properly.\n *Try relaxation or meditation techniques. These will help calm the body and get your breathing more regular. Additionally, having shortness of breath may leave you feeling anxious. These relaxation techniques will help fight the anxiety.\n *If you were previously prescribed an inhaler, you may need to use it. Pay attention to how your chest feels and what symptoms your inhaler was prescribed for.
    </string>
</resources>
